Unforgiven, I'm a villain, I'm a
Unforgiven, 내 그 길을 걸어
새 시대로 기억될 unforgiven
Yeah, what you want?
불편함이 깃든 face, wanna shut me up
사냥감을 거듭해 찾는 워리어S
너의 개임에 난 문제아
such a freak 골칫거리
Let me tell you 'bout LE SSERAFIM
내가 제일 싫은 건 낡은 대물림
어둠 속 불을 켜 마치 rebellion
We gonna kick it, break it, rules gon' give up
Unforgiven, unforgiven, yes I was bleeding
힘없이 늘 져야만 했던 싸움
but I ride
바란 적도 없어 용서 따위는
난 금기를 겨눠
Watch me now, now, now, now
Unforgiven, I'm a villain, I'm a
Unforgiven, 난 그 길을 걸어
새 시대로 기억될 unforgiven
나랑 저 너머
같이 가자, my unforgiven girl
Unforgiven, unforgiven, unforgiven
한계 위로 남겨지는 우리 이름
나랑 저 너머
같이 가자, my unforgiven girl
Unforgiven, given, given
내 스타일로 livin', livin', livin'
내 방식 아주 원 없이
또 한국말로는 아주 철없이
Get started, let's get started
미래, 그 앞에 새겨둬
나의 스토리
신념이 죄면 난 villain
I'm not the scenario
I type of a girl
Unforgiven, yes, I was bleeding
힘없이 늘 져야만 했던 싸움
But I ride
바란 적도 없어
용서 따위는 난 금기를 겨눠
Watch me now, now, now, now
Unforgiven, I'm a villain, I'm a
Unforgiven, 난 그 길을 걸어
Unforgiven, I'm a villain
새 시대로 기억될
Unforgiven
나랑 저 너머 같이 가자
Unforgiven girl
Unforgiven, Unforgiven, Unforgiven
한계 위로 남겨지는 우리 이름
나랑 저 너머 같이 가자
Unforgiven girl
Unforgiven, I'm a villain
Unforgiven, 난 그 길을 걸어
I'm a unforgiven
난 그 길을 걸어
Oh, I will never be a clown
Oh, 보게 될 거야 난
Oh, 내 목소린 좀 loud
Oh,  I don't care, just shout it out
나랑 저 너머 같이 가자
Unforgiven girl
Unforgiven, Unforgiven, Unforgiven
한계 위로 남겨지는 우리 이름
나랑 저 너머 같이 가자
Unforgiven girl
Unforgiven, Unforgiven, Unforgiven
한계 위로 남겨지는 우리 이름